<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/quick-start/</guid><description>In this guide, we will show you how to use Band to develop Android application.
Steps to use Band # Install Android Studio
Clone Android example project and open band-example/android/object_detection it with Android Studio
git clone https://github.com/mrsnu/band-example.git Change the application ID in band-example/android/object_detection/app/build.gradle to your own application ID
defaultConfig { applicationId &amp;quot;com.band.example&amp;quot; } Update the package name in band-example/android/object_detection/app/src/main/AndroidManifest.xml to your own package name
&amp;lt;manifest xmlns:android=&amp;quot;http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android&amp;quot; package=&amp;quot;com.band.example&amp;quot;&amp;gt; Change the application name in band-example/android/object_detection/app/src/main/res/values/strings.</description></item><item><title>Benchmark Tool</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/benchmark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/benchmark/</guid><description>Band provides a simple C++ binary to benchmark a runtime performance. The binary generates repeatitive model requests based on a given config file, and reports latency statistics afterwards.
How to run # [root]/script/run_benchmark.py script will build band_benchmark binary file and execute it with a specified config file. Built binary file and target config file can be found in [root]/benchmark.
On Android # If you want to build binary from docker container (Refer to [root]/script/docker_util.</description></item><item><title>Config</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/config/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/config/</guid><description>There are four configuration objects for each Band&amp;rsquo;s component.
Each configuration field is optional or required. If a field is optional, then it is guaranteed that the default value exists. If a field is required, a configuration cannot be generated by RuntimeConfigBuilder without specifying the field.
Enumeration Types # BandSchedulerType
kFixedDeviceFixedWorker kRoundRobin kShortestExpectedLatency kFixedDeviceGlobalQueue kHeterogeneousEarliestFinishTime kLeastSlackTimeFirst kHeterogeneousEarliestFinishTimeReserved CPUMaskFlags
kAll kLittle kBig kPrimary DeviceFlags
kCPU kGPU kDSP kNPU SubgraphPreparationType
kNoFallbackSubgraph kFallbackPerWorker kUnitSubgraph kMergeUnitSubgraph ProfileConfig # online [type: bool, default: true]: Profile online if true, offline if false.</description></item><item><title>Preprocessing</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/preprocessing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/preprocessing/</guid><description>Overview # Band provides a set of APIs to preprocess the data. The preprocessing is mendatory and time-consuming process to run the machine learning model on the Band. Band provides Buffer and BufferProcessor to efficiently develop the preprocessing pipeline.
Buffer is an arbitrary wrapper of the data. It wraps the data with the metadata such as image, text, and Band Tensor to be used in the preprocessing pipeline. BufferProcessor is a set of APIs to preprocess the data.</description></item><item><title>Build Guide (Advanced Users)</title><link>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/build-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://band.snu.ac.kr/docs/getting-started/build-guide/</guid><description>We provide pre-built binaries for Android and Windows. However, if you want to build Band from source code, please follow the instructions below. It is currently tested on Ubuntu 18.04 and Windows 10.
Prerequisites # We recommend using Visual Studio Code dev container to build Band. We provide the container to build Band without installing any dependencies. For more details, please refer to Visual Studio Code Dev Container. If you use the container, you can skip to Prerequisites for Android and How to build &amp;amp; run.</description></item></channel></rss>