<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Prologue on</title><link>https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/</link><description>Recent content in Prologue on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/introduction/</guid><description>Band is an efficient deep learning platform for mobile-cloud collaborative support for multiple DNNs. Band supports backend-agnostic coordination of DNN requests on heterogeneous processors in a mobile device to cloud server. Band is currently backed by following backend machine learning frameworks.
Tensorflow v2.9.2 &amp;hellip; Android ☑ iOS ☐ gRPC ☐ Band provides Java and C APIs, as well as an official plugin for Unreal Engine.
Quick Start # 👉 The Quick Start is intended for intermediate to advanced users.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/about-us/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mrsnu.github.io/docs/prologue/about-us/</guid><description>Current Members # Youngki Lee, Byung-Gon Chun
Jingyu Lee, Changmin Jeon, Minjae Kim, Hyunsoo Kim, Seonjun Kim
Previous Members # Joo Seong Jeong, Donghyun Kim, Changjin Jeong
Citation # If you find our work useful, please cite our paper below! The original codebase for paper submission is archived here
@inproceedings{jeong2022band, title={Band: coordinated multi-DNN inference on heterogeneous mobile processors}, author={Jeong, Joo Seong and Lee, Jingyu and Kim, Donghyun and Jeon, Changmin and Jeong, Changjin and Lee, Youngki and Chun, Byung-Gon}, booktitle={Proceedings of the 20th Annual International Conference on Mobile Systems, Applications and Services}, pages={235--247}, year={2022} } Acknowledgment # This work was supported by Samsung Research Funding &amp;amp; Incubation Center of Samsung Electronics under project number SRFC-IT2001-03.</description></item></channel></rss>